Guide to the Yale College, Records of the Yale Bands
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1901-2013; Accession 2015-A-063
  - Computer files
    - Yale Concert Band Raw Part 2 "Newsreel Yale Remembers World War II April 8, 1994 Woolsey Hall, 2015-A-0063-0015; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Concert Band Part 2 "Newsreel Yale Remembers World War II April 8, 1994 Woolsey Hall, 2015-A-0063-0016; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Concert Band Part 2 B&W "Newsreel Yale Remembers World War II April 8, 1994 Woolsey Hall, 2015-A-0063-0017; 1 (Box 553)
    - And the Sky and the Earth: A cantata for the Sent-Down Youth, 2015-A-0063-0018; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Concert Band Remembers Cole Porter: An American Icon, 2015-A-0063-0019; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Concert Band Remembers Cole Porter: An American Icon: DVD Master, 2015-A-0063-0020; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Concert Band Sampler DVD December 2006, 2015-A-0063-0021; 1 (Box 553)
    - Glenn Miller 2010 Sound Effects for Radio Play, 2015-A-0063-0022; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Concert Band 4/9/10, 2015-A-0063-0023; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Concert Band Projections: Pictures at an Exhibition, 2015-A-0063-0024; 1 (Box 553)
    - YCB 2/10/12 "The Silver Screen" Recordings w/projections, 2015-A-0063-0025; 1 (Box 553)
    - 1-Santos, Brazil, 2015-A-0063-0026; 1 (Box 553)
    - 2-Sorocaba, Brazil, 2015-A-0063-0027; 1 (Box 553)
    - 3-Campenas, Brazil, 2015-A-0063-0028; 1 (Box 553)
    - 4-Sao Paulo, Brazil, 2015-A-0063-0029; 1 (Box 553)
    - 5-Rio de Janeiro (1), 2015-A-0063-0030; 1 (Box 553)
    - 6-Rio de Janeiro (2), 2015-A-0063-0031; 1 (Box 553)
    - Parliament by A.A. Roberts, 2015-A-0063-0032; 1 (Box 553)
    - Cole Porter 1, 2015-A-0063-0033; 1 (Box 553)
    - [no label information] Star Wars, 2015-A-0063-0034; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Law School: A Tribute to Stan Wheeler, 2015-A-0063-0035; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Law School: 2009 Stan Wheeler Jazz Concert, 2015-A-0063-0036; 1 (Box 553)
    - Stan Wheeler Memorial Jazz Concert Friday, June 16, 2010, 2015-A-0063-0037; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Law School 2011 Stan Wheeler Memorial Jazz Concert Featuring the Yale Jazz Ensemble The Reunion Jazz Ensemble April 3, 2011, 2015-A-0063-0038; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Law School 2012 Stan Wheeler Jazz Concert Sunday April 15, 2012 Yale Jazz Ensemble The Reunion Jazz Ensemble, 2015-A-0063-0039; 1 (Box 553)
    - Movie Madness YPMB CD 2004, 2015-A-0063-0040; 1 (Box 553)
    - Georgetowm 2008 Halftime, 2015-A-0063-0041; 1 (Box 553)
    - YPMB YIR 2008 by Men, 2015-A-0063-0042; 1 (Box 553)
    - YPMB Year in Review, 2015-A-0063-0043; 1 (Box 553)
    - YBMB Class of 2012 Episode MMXII It's a Trap!, 2015-A-0063-0044; 1 (Box 553)
    - Indiana Jones and the Book of Life, 2015-A-0063-0045; 1 (Box 553)
    - YPMB for Vendetta, 2015-A-0063-0046; 1 (Box 553)
    - [no label information] YPMB 1991 and YPMB.mp3, 2015-A-0063-0047; 1 (Box 553)